

SELENA PASKALEVA social media specialist

CONTACT

331-304-2902

design@florenaandco.com

www.florenaandco.com

LANGUAGES

English

Spanish

Bulgarian

SKILLS

Content Design

Photography

Project Management

Video Editing

INTERESTS

- Passionate about aesthetics and beauty
- Content Creation

PROFILE

I am a highly skilled social media specialist and co-founder of Florena & Co. Flower Boutique, with over two and a half years of experience managing and executing social media strategies. In my role, I am responsible for all aspects of the digital presence of Florena & Co. including but not limited to advertising campaigns, photoshoots, marketing initiatives, new collections, customer engagement, and more. Over the last few years, I have steadily demonstrated creativity, engagement increase, and consistent approach in driving Florena & Co.'s online growth. I have successfully launched multiple collection campaigns and showcased my skills in marketing, social media strategizing, branding, web design, and high-quality content which clearly highlight that Florena & Co. is the solution everyone is searching for.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Social Media Specialist, Aug 2022 - Current

Harper College

Google Analytics Certificate, Oct 2023

Google

Floral Certificate, Aug 2022

European Floral Design School

High School Diploma, June 2022

Schaumburg High School

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder of Florena & Co. Flower Boutique, Sept. 2022 - Current

- Marketing
- Floral Design
- Entrepreneurship

- Develop and execute social media strategies across social media platforms such as Instagram, Facebook, Google, etc.
- Create visually impactful content, consistent with brand identity and customer engagement.
- Collaborate with floral artisans to curate novel collections.
- Oversee social media advertising budget and strategies to ensure an increase in ROI

Teacher Assistant, Campanelli Elementary School, Jan 2022 - May 2022

- Assisted in developing curriculum for fifth grade students
- Presented lessons and tutored students with new material
- Maintain organization in classroom